{"id":"2017_25","name":"Romans Lesson 252017_25","memoryVerse":"“Let everyone be subject to the governing authorities, for there is no authority except that which God has established. The authorities that exist have been established by God.” – Romans 13:1","dayQuestions":{"one":{"title":"FIRST DAY: Read the notes and the references.","questions":[{"id":"2017_25_1","questionText":"1. What was meaningful to you in the lecture?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_25_2","questionText":"2. What help did you receive from the notes?","answer":"","quotes":[]}]},"two":{"title":"SECOND DAY: Read Romans 13:8-10 with Romans 12:9-21; 1 Corinthians 13:1-8.","readVerse":[{"book":"Romans","verse":"13:8-10"},{"book":"Romans","verse":"12:9-21"},{"book":"1 Corinthians","verse":"13:1-8"}],"questions":[{"id":"2017_25_3","questionText":"3. Why can Christians never fully satisfy the continuing debt to love one another?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_25_4","questionText":"4. Compare and contrast legalistic versus loving obedience to the commands in verse 9. Which one do you lean toward?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_25_5","questionText":"5. Whom is it that you struggle to love? What does that reveal about them and you?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_25_6","questionText":"6.  How would you explain “love is the fulfillment of the law”?","answer":"","quotes":[]}]},"three":{"title":"THIRD DAY: Read Romans 13:11-12.","readVerse":[{"book":"Romans","verse":"13:11-12"}],"questions":[{"id":"2017_25_7","questionText":"7.  What does Paul mean by “salvation” and “the day is almost here”? What is Paul’s motive in reminding believers our salvation is nearer now?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_25_8","questionText":"8.  How does the Bible describe this “present time” as the Lord’s return draws nearer? (Use any Bible verses, such as Galatians 1:4; Luke 19:44.)","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"Galatians","verse":"1:4"},{"book":"Luke","verse":"19:44"}]},{"id":"2017_25_9","questionText":"  9.  List ways you see Christians slumbering presently. In what ways might you be slumbering?","answer":"","quotes":[]}]},"four":{"title":"FOURTH DAY: Read Romans 13:12-14.","readVerse":[{"book":"Romans","verse":"13:12-14"}],"questions":[{"id":"2017_25_10","questionText":"10. How has your culture normalized behaviors the Bible calls indecent?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_25_11","questionText":"11.  Using verse 13 as help, what does behaving decently look like?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_25_12","questionText":"12. How is God convicting you regarding these verses?","answer":"","quotes":[]}]},"five":{"title":"FIFTH DAY: Read Romans 13:12-14.","readVerse":[{"book":"Romans","verse":"13:12-14"}],"questions":[{"id":"2017_25_13","questionText":"13.  What is the “armor of light”? (Use Ephesians 6:10-18 and Galatians 5:22-23 to help you.)","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"Ephesians","verse":"6:10-18"},{"book":"Galatians","verse":"5:22-23"}]},{"id":"2017_25_14","questionText":"14.  How does knowing Jesus is Light help you understand His character and works? (See John 8:12; 1 John 1:5-7 or any other Scriptures you may know.)","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"John","verse":"8:12"},{"book":"1 John","verse":"1:5-7"}]},{"id":"2017_25_15","questionText":"15.  How will you clothe yourself with the Lord Jesus Christ instead of gratifying the desires of the sinful nature?","answer":"","quotes":[]}]},"six":{"title":"SIXTH DAY: Review Romans 13:8-14.","readVerse":[{"book":"Romans","verse":"13:8-14"}],"questions":[{"id":"2017_25_16","questionText":"16.  What have you learned about God in this week’s study? How may your group pray for you as you make this truth a part of your life?","answer":"","quotes":[]},{"id":"2017_25_17","questionText":"17. Homiletics for discussion and administrative leaders: Romans 13:8-14","answer":"","quotes":[{"book":"Romans","verse":"13:8-14"}]}]}}}